<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our certifications on Nuvibit - Cloud Foundation</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/</link><description>Recent content in Our certifications on Nuvibit - Cloud Foundation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022 - Nuvibit AG</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:07:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nuvibit.com/certifications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS Solution Architect Professional</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-solarchitect-professional/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:07:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-solarchitect-professional/</guid><description>This credential helps organizations identify and develop talent with critical skills for implementing cloud initiatives. Earning AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Professional validates the ability to design, deploy, and evaluate applications on AWS within diverse, complex requirements.</description></item><item><title>AWS DevOps Engineer Professional</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-devopsengineer-professional/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:06:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-devopsengineer-professional/</guid><description>This credential helps organizations identify and develop talent with critical skills for implementing cloud initiatives. Earning AWS Certified DevOps Engineer – Professional validates the ability to automate the testing and deployment of AWS infrastructure and applications.</description></item><item><title>AWS Security Speciality</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-security-speciality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:05:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-security-speciality/</guid><description>This credential helps organizations identify and develop talent with critical skills for implementing cloud initiatives. Earning AWS Certified Security – Specialty validates expertise in securing data and workloads in the AWS Cloud.</description></item><item><title>AWS Advanced Networking Speciality</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-advanced-networking-specialty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:04:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-advanced-networking-specialty/</guid><description>This credential helps organizations identify and develop talent with critical skills for implementing cloud initiatives. Earning AWS Certified Advanced Networking – Specialty validates expertise in designing and maintaining network architecture for the breadth of AWS services.</description></item><item><title>AWS Solution Architect Associate</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-solarchitect-associate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:03:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-solarchitect-associate/</guid><description>This credential helps organizations identify and develop talent with critical skills for implementing cloud initiatives. Earning AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate validates the ability to design and implement distributed systems on AWS.</description></item><item><title>AWS Developer Associate</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-developer-associate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:02:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-developer-associate/</guid><description>This credential helps organizations identify and develop talent with critical skills for implementing cloud initiatives. Earning AWS Certified Developer – Associate validates the ability to write and deploy cloud-based applications.</description></item><item><title>AWS SysOps Administrator Associate</title><link>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-sysopsadmin-associate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:01:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nuvibit.com/certifications/aws-sysopsadmin-associate/</guid><description>This credential helps organizations identify and develop talent with critical skills for implementing cloud initiatives. Earning AWS Certified SysOps Administrator – Associate demonstrates experience deploying, managing, and operating workloads on AWS.</description></item></channel></rss>